i will start off with david if you are
ready
yeah
thank you
so we were working on the client the vv2
client obviously in the previous two
weeks
and
we fixed a couple of things uh we are
trying to finalize
all the existing features in the
software
and we have a feature freeze both on the
ui and
the code as well
um
so
beside the client side
uh
for example the the changeless coin
selector has a slight problem
in it
that the guys are working on so beside
the client we're trying to optimize the
back end as well uh for example the
performance and the the
the
response time of the backhand
and these are ticking times because all
of these final
small touches on the software
without refactoring everything
always takes more time than than
before
so now we are in that phase and
we are aiming for the final version of
of 2.0
and just one more thing that according
to the current plans
we are coming with the main net release
that will be the next
the next step so there there won't be a
another
main test main testing period or
something like this
to have the release
quickly
the these two phases now
is merged together
do you want to norbo go ahead and
explain the stuff going on with the
marketing side
so we have started working on this uh
wasabi box project we had a few meetings
and
figured out what that we should put
inside the box
the other topic is the
new blog is almost ready i'm working on
it and just need some bug fixes so and
some videos and articles are also ready
and we are doing everything i think
that's all in that sub
just to highlight uh if you want to help
out with reviewing the blog posts please
do
and if you feel like coming onto a
podcast to record then please let me
know likewise and rearrange something
okay so so regarding the wasabi 2.0
market in france
can you explain
how
the release is going to go
let's say
from
the last week
before the release to the first
week after the release how do you
imagine that
like what's the big marketing plan there
what's the schedule prepare everything
in advance
or at least as much as reasonable um
contacts and texts ready for the
announcement emails to all the news also
outlets and whatnot then
prepare for for the live release event
uh for this you gotta invite guests
mainly and maybe you want to have at
least some time
slot management to make it reasonable
but maybe a free-for-all would be fun
too who knows yeah then we make the we
start the live show maybe two hours
before the release we talk about wasabi
get everyone excited
and then david pushes the button live on
stage and
people go download uh and check it out
and we continue having conversations uh
bringing new guests on on board to talk
about wasabi and
eventually the first coin join happens i
know an hour after or two hours after
we release the software who knows
and then we look at it on air and that's
kind of the
the end of the live ceremony i guess so
probably five hours or something like
this of continuous yeah live stream and
in the meantime we send out the armada
of emails to all the outlets uh with
with the articles and announcements um
the blog posts go out
uh announcing the 2.0 mainnet release
and maybe one additional
blog post goes a couple minutes later i
don't know and
yeah i would like to have also at least
one
big bitcoin podcast release an episode
uh when we act like on the day that we
release
that would be pretty cool yeah i guess
that's the timeline all right thank you
oh yeah i think i forgot is the the swag
boxes i guess we'll see how fast we can
get everything printed and shipped and
delivered uh but it would be cool if we
can send out the physical packages i
guess at least three days before the
actual release maybe five days before
something like that just so that there's
enough time for the packages to arrive
at most people so yeah i guess that's
something that we will check back on in
two weeks uh on the 15th how the
the swag box is going and if we will
ship it out together with the release or
a bit later um i guess uh
one general question
uh
do you think we should start with more
blog posts already the week before the
release or should like you know be kind
of a
period of excitement before the release
or should the big blog post come only
with the release itself i think the blog
posts um like having them go out is
great but it's it's not as interactive
as some of the other things so you know
if there's videos or some other content
that's not just reading i think that's
even better so it's going to be a
concerted effort between the blog posts
the youtube videos
and then on top of that the articles and
stuff that other people are publishing
how much emphasis should be put on the
blog post i don't think is as important
and the timing of that
um it should just be 2.0 is out the blog
post comes out as soon as we push the
button
you know here it is
and then it's really the twitter's job
and like youtube and all these other
outlets job to spread the news
uh for the actual release we're going to
have that live announcement party it
might be cool to have a physical
party in the office uh on that day uh
and we might invite people who want to
join um i know but was pretty cool
atmosphere last time during the first
release candidate
uh so
we could replicate that and just have a
you know a
microphone in there so that people can
come join the live stream
yeah i mean
yeah if you if the office people think
that there's going to be a bunch of
people in budapest at that time and it's
a it's a
final closing something right closing
the development
with uh
meet space event
what's up with the ui
exactly what i was about to
ask hello guys hello
okay so um dan and roland are not around
so i'm going to sub for them to deport
today um
last week in ui team we have
but basically there's only minor fixes
that are going on
um
but um
we are planning to fix um
uh
a couple of things like um showing times
in the music box control
and i am also working on fixing the high
gpu usage on idle which i think i have i
may have sold
unless um adam proves otherwise
and um
and also adding some
tweaks to the history
um data grid
and also to finalize any open uh open
prs as well
so all in all our things are going
smoothly
okay thank you
are there any other questions for the ui
team
i think basically everything important
is figured also
pretty good on the ui from everything
from now on it's just candy and sugar on
top
uh david i think last week you asked
about getting some like newbie
input on using the wallet
was there anybody that was able to
volunteer and do that with you
i'm not sure what was about newbie input
using the wallet
first time user experience i'm guessing
is what then the last exactly i actually
remember that conversation and the
resolution was that roland's girlfriend
is going to beat upon
so maybe you want to ask roland about
that
good
i wanted to make sure it was uh taken
care of but that's my main point or main
main goal is if it was resolved i mean
for like i've been doing this for a
while uh already with a couple of people
not many just a handful
and that influenced a lot of my feedback
very good
anything else
we can go into the general topics and
conversations
max you're coming to the lightning
ground discussion yes
i wanted to ask about something not
related to 2.0 but just
since everybody is here i know that
there was the work swap that we were
doing a few weeks ago and it's been
kind of dead in the water the last
couple of weeks
with everything
i think this is just one of those
conversations that uh
i know that everybody's busy it's kind
of fizzled out as far as interest so the
question is should it continue or should
we ask it or should this conversation be
brought up in another meeting elsewhere
so my hope was that the new people are
going to come
there and
and they can get
they can learn about a lot of things
right but it seems like the new people
are not really coming there
it's the same same world
so i did not meet anyone on on the
on the conversations right i did not
meet anyone who i didn't already know
and talk about it
in that case then i think that we can uh
brainstorm or talk about some other ways
to get this happening whether it's you
know just getting them to join in on the
2.0 calls or doing something else but
you know somehow finding a way for it to
be
participated in so
we can talk about this in another
meeting or another uh
conversations privately i just unless
people have ideas that they wanted to
suggest
i think also that preparing 2.0 is not
so helpful regarding that
workshop
concept
because
in the last
two weeks
i just don't felt i have time to
didn't feel to have time to go there
so maybe that's it's timing it's a
timing problem as well
the prior the prior thing is that fatada
mentioned that
i was enjoyed doing it so i think the
concept itself is not bad
it's just that
we did not reach the peak
attention of the people
i think then it can be a combination of
the two we can probably revisit this uh
after 2.0 is released so that way
everybody can focus on getting this done
i think everybody's got enough to do
and then
you know maybe another let's say two
weeks or three weeks after release so
that way we can get all the bugs worked
out and make sure that it's not
nothing's going crazy
so whatever that would be june we can uh
talk about getting this going in some
other way or format
that's everything then
i will see all of you guys later next
week we'll have our meeting as usual and
uh
look forward to seeing everyone then
good luck
see you bye